<Annotation corpus="brat-project-final">
  <Proposition id="T1">
    <ADU type="conclusion"/>
    <text>students can acquire university knowledge without the prerequisite of passing exam</text>
    <TextPosition start="400" end="482"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T3">
    <ADU type="claim"/>
    <text>not only is every students expert in every part of one subject but also it will reduce the student in the campus who leave uncultivated</text>
    <TextPosition start="2224" end="2359"/>
    <Relation relationID="RT3-T1" type="Default Inference" typeBinary="0" partnerID="T1"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T4">
    <ADU type="premise"/>
    <text>I don't like electronics</text>
    <TextPosition start="637" end="661"/>
    <Relation relationID="T6Default Inference" type="Default Inference" typeBinary="0" partnerID="T6"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T5">
    <ADU type="premise"/>
    <text>electronics cannot always be seen in the real world</text>
    <TextPosition start="671" end="722"/>
    <Relation relationID="T4Default Inference" type="Default Inference" typeBinary="0" partnerID="T4"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T6">
    <ADU type="claim"/>
    <text>the students are not constantly expert in every part of a subject</text>
    <TextPosition start="537" end="602"/>
    <Relation relationID="RT6-T1" type="Default Inference" typeBinary="0" partnerID="T1"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T7">
    <ADU type="premise"/>
    <text>And I have had 0 in physics score when I study the electronics</text>
    <TextPosition start="724" end="786"/>
    <Relation relationID="T6Default Inference" type="Default Inference" typeBinary="0" partnerID="T6"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T8">
    <ADU type="premise"/>
    <text>But I constantly achieve 100 score when I study other part of the physics</text>
    <TextPosition start="788" end="861"/>
    <Relation relationID="T6Default Inference" type="Default Inference" typeBinary="0" partnerID="T6"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T9">
    <ADU type="premise"/>
    <text>And if I cannot attend the classes until I pass the exam of electronics, I could not pass the entire part of physics, and I will fail the exam over and over again</text>
    <TextPosition start="863" end="1025"/>
    <Relation relationID="T6Default Inference" type="Default Inference" typeBinary="0" partnerID="T6"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T10">
    <ADU type="premise"/>
    <text>Luckily, in our university, you can attend the classes regardless of the score you reach</text>
    <TextPosition start="1027" end="1115"/>
    <Relation relationID="T6Default Inference" type="Default Inference" typeBinary="0" partnerID="T6"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T11">
    <ADU type="premise"/>
    <text>And I can study physics without consideration of my electronics</text>
    <TextPosition start="1117" end="1180"/>
    <Relation relationID="T6Default Inference" type="Default Inference" typeBinary="0" partnerID="T6"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T12">
    <ADU type="premise"/>
    <text>And at last, I took the electronics again and pass the exam</text>
    <TextPosition start="1182" end="1241"/>
    <Relation relationID="T6Default Inference" type="Default Inference" typeBinary="0" partnerID="T6"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T13">
    <ADU type="claim"/>
    <text>the university student may don't reach a high if the university allow student to participate in the class no matter whether they pass the test or not</text>
    <TextPosition start="1874" end="2023"/>
    <Relation relationID="RT13T1" type="Default Conflict" typeBinary="1" partnerID="T1"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T14">
    <ADU type="premise"/>
    <text>the benefit of free to access to the classes eclipse the issue of lower points</text>
    <TextPosition start="2029" end="2107"/>
    <Relation relationID="T13Default Conflict" type="Default Conflict" typeBinary="1" partnerID="T13"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T15">
    <ADU type="claim"/>
    <text>if the university take the policy that no one can attend the classes without passing exam, students are highly likely to leave uncultivated</text>
    <TextPosition start="1253" end="1392"/>
    <Relation relationID="RT15-T1" type="Default Inference" typeBinary="0" partnerID="T1"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T16">
    <ADU type="premise"/>
    <text>If one fail most of the exam, it means that he or she cannot participate in most of the classes</text>
    <TextPosition start="1394" end="1489"/>
    <Relation relationID="T15Default Inference" type="Default Inference" typeBinary="0" partnerID="T15"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T17">
    <ADU type="premise"/>
    <text>And the students will have nothing to do in the campus</text>
    <TextPosition start="1491" end="1545"/>
    <Relation relationID="T15Default Inference" type="Default Inference" typeBinary="0" partnerID="T15"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T18">
    <ADU type="premise"/>
    <text>he or she will play online games days and nights</text>
    <TextPosition start="1552" end="1600"/>
    <Relation relationID="T15Default Inference" type="Default Inference" typeBinary="0" partnerID="T15"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T19">
    <ADU type="premise"/>
    <text>The academic achievement will decline</text>
    <TextPosition start="1602" end="1639"/>
    <Relation relationID="T15Default Inference" type="Default Inference" typeBinary="0" partnerID="T15"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T20">
    <ADU type="premise"/>
    <text>this student will become a loser in the world</text>
    <TextPosition start="1653" end="1698"/>
    <Relation relationID="T15Default Inference" type="Default Inference" typeBinary="0" partnerID="T15"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T21">
    <ADU type="premise"/>
    <text>And all this is due to that the university don't permit them to attend the class</text>
    <TextPosition start="1700" end="1780"/>
    <Relation relationID="T15Default Inference" type="Default Inference" typeBinary="0" partnerID="T15"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T22">
    <ADU type="premise"/>
    <text>This is not the failure of the university but also the entire education system</text>
    <TextPosition start="1782" end="1860"/>
    <Relation relationID="T15Default Inference" type="Default Inference" typeBinary="0" partnerID="T15"/>
  </Proposition>
  <OriginalText>It is not necessary for university students to attend classes

Though out the last decade, the load of the university students has been constantly increasing. There are those who consider that university students cannot attend any classes until the students pass the exam. There are those who said that student can attend the university coarse without passing the exam. However, from my perspective, students can acquire university knowledge without the prerequisite of passing exam. The reasons to be illustrated are follows. 
Firstly, the students are not constantly expert in every part of a subject. For example, I love Physics. But I don't like electronics, because electronics cannot always be seen in the real world. And I have had 0 in physics score when I study the electronics. But I constantly achieve 100 score when I study other part of the physics. And if I cannot attend the classes until I pass the exam of electronics, I could not pass the entire part of physics, and I will fail the exam over and over again. Luckily, in our university, you can attend the classes regardless of the score you reach. And I can study physics without consideration of my electronics. And at last, I took the electronics again and pass the exam.
Secondly, if the university take the policy that no one can attend the classes without passing exam, students are highly likely to leave uncultivated. If one fail most of the exam, it means that he or she cannot participate in most of the classes. And the students will have nothing to do in the campus. Then he or she will play online games days and nights. The academic achievement will decline. In the end, this student will become a loser in the world. And all this is due to that the university don't permit them to attend the class. This is not the failure of the university but also the entire education system.
Admittedly, the university student may don't reach a high if the university allow student to participate in the class no matter whether they pass the test or not. But the benefit of free to access to the classes eclipse the issue of lower points.
All in all, the university should allow the student to participate in the classed without passing the test because not only is every students expert in every part of one subject but also it will reduce the student in the campus who leave uncultivated.</OriginalText>
</Annotation>
