<Annotation corpus="brat-project-final">
  <Proposition id="T1">
    <ADU type="conclusion"/>
    <text>strict laws, like capital punishment, are essential in a society</text>
    <TextPosition start="252" end="316"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T4">
    <ADU type="claim"/>
    <text>Capital punishment helps to safeguard human rights in a strict and effective manner</text>
    <TextPosition start="1871" end="1954"/>
    <Relation relationID="RT4-T1" type="Default Inference" typeBinary="0" partnerID="T1"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T5">
    <ADU type="claim"/>
    <text>capital punishment protects the society from hardcore criminals</text>
    <TextPosition start="589" end="652"/>
    <Relation relationID="RT5-T1" type="Default Inference" typeBinary="0" partnerID="T1"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T6">
    <ADU type="premise"/>
    <text>When a criminal becomes a threat to the society, such that they can commit heinous crimes, then they are given capital punishment</text>
    <TextPosition start="452" end="581"/>
    <Relation relationID="T5Default Inference" type="Default Inference" typeBinary="0" partnerID="T5"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T7">
    <ADU type="premise"/>
    <text>Capital punishment is given only in the "rarest of the rare" cases</text>
    <TextPosition start="318" end="384"/>
    <Relation relationID="T5Default Inference" type="Default Inference" typeBinary="0" partnerID="T5"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T8">
    <ADU type="premise"/>
    <text>Its first and foremost objective is safety of other human beings</text>
    <TextPosition start="386" end="450"/>
    <Relation relationID="T5Default Inference" type="Default Inference" typeBinary="0" partnerID="T5"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T9">
    <ADU type="claim"/>
    <text>the rate of crime and violence is effectively decreased</text>
    <TextPosition start="847" end="902"/>
    <Relation relationID="RT9-T1" type="Default Inference" typeBinary="0" partnerID="T1"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T10">
    <ADU type="premise"/>
    <text>capital punishment curbs the inspiration and prospects of other hateful crimes</text>
    <TextPosition start="664" end="742"/>
    <Relation relationID="T9Default Inference" type="Default Inference" typeBinary="0" partnerID="T9"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T11">
    <ADU type="premise"/>
    <text>When a criminal mind knows the quantum of punishment, they will fear and not commit such crimes</text>
    <TextPosition start="744" end="839"/>
    <Relation relationID="T9Default Inference" type="Default Inference" typeBinary="0" partnerID="T9"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T12">
    <ADU type="premise"/>
    <text>capital punishment saves a lot of government funding which is wasted in maintenance of these hardcore criminals</text>
    <TextPosition start="917" end="1028"/>
    <Relation relationID="T13Default Inference" type="Default Inference" typeBinary="0" partnerID="T13"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T13">
    <ADU type="claim"/>
    <text>Criminals who don't have any chance of improvement or who have a past record of such crimes are, therefore, given capital punishment</text>
    <TextPosition start="1030" end="1162"/>
    <Relation relationID="RT13-T1" type="Default Inference" typeBinary="0" partnerID="T1"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T15">
    <ADU type="claim"/>
    <text>They can make mistakes which can sometimes affect an innocent, circumstantially marred criminals</text>
    <TextPosition start="1270" end="1366"/>
    <Relation relationID="RT15T1" type="Default Conflict" typeBinary="1" partnerID="T1"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T14">
    <ADU type="premise"/>
    <text>the jury giving the verdict are also humans</text>
    <TextPosition start="1173" end="1216"/>
    <Relation relationID="T15Default Inference" type="Default Inference" typeBinary="0" partnerID="T15"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T16">
    <ADU type="premise"/>
    <text>They have the life of a person at their discretion</text>
    <TextPosition start="1218" end="1268"/>
    <Relation relationID="T15Default Inference" type="Default Inference" typeBinary="0" partnerID="T15"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T17">
    <ADU type="premise"/>
    <text>The jury must therefore, take into account the circumstances of committing a crime</text>
    <TextPosition start="1368" end="1450"/>
    <Relation relationID="T15Default Inference" type="Default Inference" typeBinary="0" partnerID="T15"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T18">
    <ADU type="premise"/>
    <text>if an individual murders someone for self-defense, then such a crime is not heinous</text>
    <TextPosition start="1465" end="1548"/>
    <Relation relationID="T17Default Inference" type="Default Inference" typeBinary="0" partnerID="T17"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T19">
    <ADU type="premise"/>
    <text>Only deserving criminals, who commit such hateful crimes in their proper senses are subjected to capital punishment</text>
    <TextPosition start="1550" end="1665"/>
    <Relation relationID="T17Default Inference" type="Default Inference" typeBinary="0" partnerID="T17"/>
  </Proposition>
  <OriginalText>Capital punishment - necessary or not

Crime is always punishable. Retribution is the method for countering criminals. Some countries have stringent rules, like capital punishment, while other have a lot of flexibility in the judicial system. However, strict laws, like capital punishment, are essential in a society.
Capital punishment is given only in the "rarest of the rare" cases. Its first and foremost objective is safety of other human beings. When a criminal becomes a threat to the society, such that they can commit heinous crimes, then they are given capital punishment. Thus, capital punishment protects the society from hardcore criminals.
Moreover, capital punishment curbs the inspiration and prospects of other hateful crimes. When a criminal mind knows the quantum of punishment, they will fear and not commit such crimes. Thus, the rate of crime and violence is effectively decreased.
Importantly, capital punishment saves a lot of government funding which is wasted in maintenance of these hardcore criminals. Criminals who don't have any chance of improvement or who have a past record of such crimes are, therefore, given capital punishment.
However, the jury giving the verdict are also humans. They have the life of a person at their discretion. They can make mistakes which can sometimes affect an innocent, circumstantially marred criminals. The jury must therefore, take into account the circumstances of committing a crime. For example, if an individual murders someone for self-defense, then such a crime is not heinous. Only deserving criminals, who commit such hateful crimes in their proper senses are subjected to capital punishment.
Capital punishment is essential to control violence in the society. I firmly believe that psychopaths, terrorists or any other criminal who lacks empathy for other human lives deserve capital punishment. Capital punishment helps to safeguard human rights in a strict and effective manner. However, it should be considered as the last option by the jury and all circumstances must be taken into account before pronouncing the final verdict.
</OriginalText>
</Annotation>
