<Annotation corpus="brat-project-final">
  <Proposition id="T1">
    <ADU type="conclusion"/>
    <text>its better that people learn foreign language in their own country</text>
    <TextPosition start="354" end="420"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T3">
    <ADU type="claim"/>
    <text>It is cost effective and there is a pool of opportunities available now to accomplish the same</text>
    <TextPosition start="1722" end="1816"/>
    <Relation relationID="RT3-T1" type="Default Inference" typeBinary="0" partnerID="T1"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T4">
    <ADU type="premise"/>
    <text>In the earlier periods, it was not easy to find a teacher to learn a foreign languge</text>
    <TextPosition start="666" end="750"/>
    <Relation relationID="T5Default Conflict" type="Default Conflict" typeBinary="1" partnerID="T5"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T5">
    <ADU type="claim"/>
    <text>with the advent of globalization, one can easily find a teacher in their own country</text>
    <TextPosition start="756" end="840"/>
    <Relation relationID="RT5-T1" type="Default Inference" typeBinary="0" partnerID="T1"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T6">
    <ADU type="premise"/>
    <text>in Indian sub-continent there are large number of centers opened for getting trained in variety of languages like french, german etc</text>
    <TextPosition start="855" end="987"/>
    <Relation relationID="T5Default Inference" type="Default Inference" typeBinary="0" partnerID="T5"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T7">
    <ADU type="claim"/>
    <text>it is not possible for everyone to visit a foreign country to learn a foreign language</text>
    <TextPosition start="519" end="605"/>
    <Relation relationID="RT7-T1" type="Default Inference" typeBinary="0" partnerID="T1"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T8">
    <ADU type="premise"/>
    <text>it requires large amount of money and legal formalities</text>
    <TextPosition start="609" end="664"/>
    <Relation relationID="T7Default Inference" type="Default Inference" typeBinary="0" partnerID="T7"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T9">
    <ADU type="claim"/>
    <text>it is very easy to learn a foreign in our own country</text>
    <TextPosition start="1184" end="1237"/>
    <Relation relationID="RT9-T1" type="Default Inference" typeBinary="0" partnerID="T1"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T10">
    <ADU type="premise"/>
    <text>Students can choose any language from the set of languages available at a university</text>
    <TextPosition start="1094" end="1178"/>
    <Relation relationID="T9Default Inference" type="Default Inference" typeBinary="0" partnerID="T9"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T11">
    <ADU type="premise"/>
    <text>colleges and universities have introduced foreign language course as a part of their curriculum</text>
    <TextPosition start="997" end="1092"/>
    <Relation relationID="T9Default Inference" type="Default Inference" typeBinary="0" partnerID="T9"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T12">
    <ADU type="premise"/>
    <text>highly qualified foreign language teachers are easily accessible in various schools and colleges</text>
    <TextPosition start="1245" end="1341"/>
    <Relation relationID="T9Default Inference" type="Default Inference" typeBinary="0" partnerID="T9"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T13">
    <ADU type="premise"/>
    <text>A large number of foreign language courses are available online and there are various forums where people can discuss their problems on different foreign languages</text>
    <TextPosition start="1472" end="1635"/>
    <Relation relationID="T14Default Inference" type="Default Inference" typeBinary="0" partnerID="T14"/>
  </Proposition>
  <Proposition id="T14">
    <ADU type="claim"/>
    <text>technology has also played a great role in reducing the separation between learning a foreign languge in our own country</text>
    <TextPosition start="1350" end="1470"/>
    <Relation relationID="RT14-T1" type="Default Inference" typeBinary="0" partnerID="T1"/>
  </Proposition>
  <OriginalText>Which is better- Learning foreign language in home or host country?

Our World has varied cultures and each culture has its own language. It has become essential for a person to learn at least one foreign language as one do interacts with foreigners once in a lifetime and learning a foreign langauge adds on to a person skill-set as well. Also, I think its better that people learn foreign language in their own country. The reasons for holding that opinion are illustrated in the subsequent paragraphs.
First of all, it is not possible for everyone to visit a foreign country to learn a foreign language as it requires large amount of money and legal formalities. In the earlier periods, it was not easy to find a teacher to learn a foreign languge. But with the advent of globalization, one can easily find a teacher in their own country. For example, in Indian sub-continent there are large number of centers opened for getting trained in variety of languages like french, german etc.
Second, colleges and universities have introduced foreign language course as a part of their curriculum. Students can choose any language from the set of languages available at a university. So, it is very easy to learn a foreign in our own country. Also, highly qualified foreign language teachers are easily accessible in various schools and colleges.
Third, technology has also played a great role in reducing the separation between learning a foreign languge in our own country. A large number of foreign language courses are available online and there are various forums where people can discuss their problems on different foreign languages.
To sum up, it is better for people to learn a foreign language in their own country. It is cost effective and there is a pool of opportunities available now to accomplish the same.</OriginalText>
</Annotation>
